Jake Boes (he/him). UX Designer | Denver, Colorado.

Phone: 970-456-2929 | Email: <u>boesjake@gmail.com</u> LinkedIn: <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakeboes/</u> Portfolio: <u>jakeboes.com</u>

SUMMARY

A multi-disciplinary and creative designer with leadership experience, and a recent graduate of the University of Denver UX/UI program. Proficient in a wide array of design tools and techniques complemented by a passion for human centered design and collaboration.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technical: Figma; Adobe Creative Cloud; WebFlow; Miro; ChatGPT; Reaper; FabFilter; iZotope; HTML; CSS; GitHub; Bootstrap

UX Skills: Atomic design; UI design; color theory; heuristic evaluation; competitive analysis; typography; interaction design; storyboarding; decision flow diagrams; user need identification; user research; persona creation; insight synthesis; card sorting; information architecture; wireframing; prototyping; usability testing

Sound Skills: Music production; songwriting; sound design; pre-production; audio engineering;

UX PROJECTS

SundropAl

Led a team of three UX Designers to improve the user experience of artificial intelligence applications by designing an accessible & friendly multimodal user interface.

- Role: Lead UX Designer
- Skills/Technologies Used: User Research & Analysis, Persona, User Experience Design,
 Interaction Design, Prototyping, User Testing, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Firefly, ChatGPT

Hey Denver Redesign

Hey Denver is a queer-centered non-profit STI testing clinic and sexual health resource in Denver, CO. Our UX redesign focused on increasing usability & inclusivity of their web presence.

- Role: UX Designer
- Skills/Technologies Used: User Research & Analysis, Persona, User Experience Design, Information Architecture, Responsive Prototyping, User Testing, Figma, Photoshop

TableTips

A user-friendly board game companion app, focused on enhancing user experience by assisting in the discovery and learning of new games.

• Role: UX Designer

• Skills/Technologies Used: User Research & Analysis, Persona, User Experience Design, Insight Analysis, Prototyping, User Testing, Figma, Photoshop, Miro

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Manager, Lead Designer HORRID

2019-Present Denver. CO

Leading the creative direction and design of products, graphics, branding materials, and identity of the HORRID brand. Overseeing product development from concept to launch, while also managing collaborations with artists and maintaining the highest standards of quality.

- Designed the Horrid logo and visual style, which is used in all Horrid branding, signage, and packaging.
- Curate, design, and write for Horrid Magazine, a publication featuring dark art from international artists.
- Designing and developing a variety of products including candles, perfumes, apparel, art pieces, lotions, jewelry, and more, iterating upon and improving those products.
- Collaborating with stakeholders to develop products and offerings that align with Horrid's identity and appeal to Horrid's audience.

Studio Assistant, Audio Engineer The Band Cave Studios

2021-Present Denver, CO

Aiding and providing support for artists at a hybrid recording and rehearsal studio, while maintaining and repairing essential stupid equipment.

- Assisting the lead engineer with recording, set-up & tear down, as well as coordinating with artists to ensure productive and smooth studio sessions.
- Serving as the point of contact for booking and managing rehearsal studio sessions.
- Maintaining and repairing musical equipment such as amplifiers, cables, drums, mixers, loudspeakers, and microphones.

Freelance Graphic Designer & Music Producer Jake Bones Music & Design

2015-Present Denver, CO

Designed graphics and merchandise, recorded audio, produced tracks, mixed & mastered songs, and assisted in the songwriting process for a variety of artists, managers, and promoters.

- Managed multiple design and recording projects simultaneously, setting and meeting deadlines while developing relationships with clients and artists.
- Collaborating with clients to develop cohesive visual, audio, and marketing materials consistent with client branding and vision.

EDUCATION

Certificate, UX/UI Design | University of Denver, Denver, CO Studied UX/UI design, focusing on accessibility & usability.

Received 2023

PTCB Certification | Denver Pharmacy School, Denver, CO Studied pharmacology, drug interactions, and medical regulations.

Received 2012